[{"question": "  \u0091cause every time i see your face, i can\u0092t help but fall from grace. i know.....", "answer": " wow! this girl is good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh-ho yeah! a song with rhyming words. oo, i never thought of that before.", "answer": " i like her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  why? because she can sing and play guitar and do both at the same time?", "answer": " well, that\u0092s pretty much all i\u0092m looking for from these people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  look at you. all jealous.", "answer": " yeah pheebs, come on, you two have completely different styles. y'know, she\u0092s more.. y'know, and you\u0092re more", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  beside meeeee-eeee-ee. .", "answer": " okay, see, see, everyone else is happy she\u0092s done.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " hey phoebe.", "answer": " hey leslie, how\u0092d you know i\u0092d be here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i ran into vlad at the place where they sell the big fish, and he said you played here a lot, so umm....", "answer": "  all right listen, i have to go to the bathroom, but if the place with the big fish comes up again. i\u0092d like know whether that\u0092s several big fish or just one big fish.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  so ah, phoebe tells us you write jingles.", "answer": " actually i said she abandoned me to write jingles.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  ah, anything we might of heard of?", "answer": " ah, yeah, umm.  home is never far away.. monica, ross, and joey:  home is home star stew.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah, but, i don\u0092t do that anymore. i got kinda sick of it, and then i couldn\u0092t come up with anything good, so they fired me.", "answer": " hmm, bummer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, i y'know, i was just, umm, i was just thinking and hoping, that umm, maybe you\u0092d want to get back together?", "answer": " no. but thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " aw come on phoebe would you just think about it?", "answer": " okay. no. but thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  wow, that was kinda brutal.", "answer": " well okay, let this be a lesson to all of you, all right. once you, once you betray me, i become like the ice woman, y\u0092know. very cold, hard, unyielding, y'know nothing, nothing can penetrate this icy exterior.  can i have a tissue, please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  someone in there?", "answer": " no. this is just part of a dare devil game that i play called \u0091wait until the last moment before i burst and die.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " jeez, man did you fall.. hi! so ah, did ya, did-did-did ya fall high?", "answer": " someone was in the lady's room, i couldn\u0092t wait. i left the lid up for ya though.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  y'know what gunther, go ah, go ahead, i\u0092m-i\u0092m talking to ah, .  this is the part where you say your name.", "answer": " ginger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ginger. i\u0092m talking to ginger, so....", "answer": " don\u0092t you have to use the bathroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " where\u0092s chandler?", "answer": " ah, he can\u0092t make it, he said he had to his...  whoa-oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi, sweetie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " hi, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yeah, huh.", "answer": " i\u0092ve got some bad news.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i can get a quick bite to eat, but then i have to come back up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " come on sweetie! you\u0092ve had to work late every night for the past two weeks, what is it this time?", "answer": " actually, it\u0092s kinda my fault. i-i quit today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  but work comes first!  oh hey, but that\u0092s sad about you though, what happened? burn out? burn all out, did ya?", "answer": " nooo, he\u0092s leaving for a better job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh well that\u0092s great, so i guess this is ah, this is good bye then. huh?  good bye.", "answer": " okay, then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " well we\u0092re gonna miss you around here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " so, see ya on saturday.", "answer": " yeah, you bet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " y'know those are a delicacy in india.", "answer": " yeah, that was leslie calling again to see if we can get back together. that\u0092s the twentieth time today! and good luck leslie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " wow, she must have hurt you pretty bad, huh?", "answer": " well, yeah. y'know, we were best friends, ever since we were little, our moms worked on the barge together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh, you two must have been so cute running around on a barge.", "answer": " you never run on a barge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  hey. phoebe and monica: hey.", "answer": " is ah, is chandler around?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " no, umm, he met some girl at the coffee house.", "answer": " oooh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yeah, ginger something.", "answer": " nooo. no, no, ah, are you sure it wasn\u0092t something that sounded like ginger, like ah, gingeer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " no, it was ginger. i remember, because when he told me, i said,  \u0091the movie star.\u0092", "answer": " aww, man. that\u0092s the girl i was hiding from. when she finds out he\u0092s my roommate, she\u0092s gonna tell him what i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well, what did you do?", "answer": " what, oh, oh, oh, no, no, i can\u0092t, i can\u0092t tell you that, it\u0092s like the most awful, horrible thing i\u0092ve ever done my whole life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " y'know what, don\u0092t tell us. we\u0092ll just wait until chandler gets home,  because it\u0092ll be more fun that way.", "answer": " all right!! okay, it was like four years ago. okay, ginger and i had gone out a few times, and then this one weekend, we went up to her dad\u0092s cabin. just me, her, and her annoying little dog pepper. well that night, i cooked this really romantic dinner....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " you gave her food poisoning!?", "answer": " i wish. no. after dinner, me, her, and pepper all fell asleep in front of the fire. well i woke up in the middle of the night and i saw that the fire was dying out. so, i picked up a log and threw it on. or, at least what i thought was a log.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh my god!! you threw pepper on the fire!", "answer": " i wish. see, i guess another thing i probably should\u0092ve told you about ginger is that she kinda has a ah, artificial leg.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " oh my god! joey, what did you do after you threw her leg on the fire?", "answer": " i ran!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " well, that\u0092s the best kiss i\u0092ve had with anyone i\u0092ve ever met in a men\u0092s room.", "answer": " actually, me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  op, foot in a puddle, foot all in a puddle.", "answer": " oh damn, i hate that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " yeah, we\u0092re gonna have to get you out of those shoes.", "answer": " oh, don\u0092t worry about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no, really you\u0092re gonna freeze.", "answer": " no, i\u0092m not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " you\u0092re not, what do you, what do you got a bionic foot?", "answer": " some day, maybe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " funny book?", "answer": " hmmm. oh, no, no, i just thinking about something funny i heard today. umm, mark, mark saying \u0091i\u0092ll see you saturday.\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yeah, at the lecture, i told you that last week, you said you didn\u0092t mind.", "answer": " oh, no, no, no, it\u0092s-it\u0092s not the lecture ah, i mind, umm....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh, please tell me it\u0092s not because i\u0092m going with mark.", "answer": " oh, well...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh my god!!! ross!!", "answer": " well, i\u0092m sorry, but ah, look if you\u0092re not working with him anymore, why do you have to still do stuff with him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " because, he\u0092s my friend.", "answer": " okay, but do you really need another friend? i mean...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " okay, well if i stop playing with joey and chandler, can i play with mark?", "answer": " is that funny? am i supposed to be laughing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, you thought \u0091see you saturday\u0092 was funny. look honey, mark is in fashion okay, i like having a friend that i can share this stuff with. you guys would never want to go to a lecture with me.", "answer": " pa-haa!! i would love to go with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " really!?", "answer": " yeah, hey i-i have clothes, i even pick them out. i mean for, for all you know i could be a fashion..... monger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " okay. honey, i would love for you to go with me.  what?", "answer": " what should i wear, now i\u0092m all nervous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " y'know they say a watched pot never beeps.", "answer": " it\u0092s just y'know, been a couple of hours, and she hasn\u0092t called. not that i even care, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " phoebe why don\u0092t you just call her? you obviously want to.", "answer": " you think you know me so well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " well, don\u0092t \u0091cha wanna?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " okay, well i do know you.", "answer": " that\u0092s what i said.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " well so?", "answer": " i can\u0092t. i can\u0092t. she dumped me, i mean i totally trusted her and then one day it was \u0091okay, bye pheebs\u0092 gone. y'know what the saddest part is, when we were playing together, that was like the most fun i\u0092ve ever had in like all my lives.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " we\u0092re beginning to see a lot of layering of sheer fabrics and colours. for instance a sheer navy blouse over a pink....", "answer": "  i\u0092m really glad we came.  you\u0092re so pretty. i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  smelly cat, smelly cat, what are they feeding you? smelly cat, smelly cat, it\u0092s not your fault.", "answer": " wow, that\u0092s great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh, yeah!", "answer": " y'know you could totally sell this. it\u0092d be perfect for like umm, a kitty litter campaign.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " i..., a jingle? no, no-no-no, no.", "answer": " what? why not? you could make a ton of money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " okay, well if i was in this for the money, i\u0092d be a millionaire by now, y'know. you just got to get out of that jingle head sweetie.", "answer": " aw, you\u0092re right, you\u0092re right. i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh, can i borrow this?  my milk\u0092s gone bad.", "answer": " oh, i hate that. i once had a thing of half and half, stole my car.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " so umm, how was your date with ginger?", "answer": " great. it was great. she\u0092s ah, she\u0092s great, great looking, great personality, she\u0092s greatness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " sounds like she\u0092s got the ah, whole package.", "answer": " joey told you about the leg, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " oh god, it freaked me out. okay, i know it shouldn\u0092t have, but it did. i mean i like her, i don\u0092t want to stop seeing her, but every so often it\u0092s like \u0091hey, y'know what, where\u0092s your leg?\u0092 i mean i\u0092m the smallest person in the world aren\u0092t i? i\u0092m the smallest person in the world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  morning.", "answer": "  actually he\u0092s the smallest person in the world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  heard about the leg burnin\u0092 huh?", "answer": " it came up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  so i nodded off a little.", "answer": " nodded off!! ross you were snoring. my father\u0092s boat didn\u0092t make that much noise when it hit rocks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " come on! forty-five minutes! forty-five minutes the man talked about strappy backed dresses.", "answer": " well okay, how about four hours in a freezing museum auditorium listening to professor pitstains and he\u0092s \u0091hey everybody! remember that thing that\u0092s been dead for a gazillion years. well there\u0092s this little bone we didn\u0092t know it had!\u0092", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " first of all it\u0092s professor pittain! and second of all, that little bone, proved that, that particular dinosaur had wings, but didn\u0092t fly.", "answer": " okay, see now, what i just heard: blah-blah-blah, blah-blah-blah-blah-blah, blah-blah-blah, blah, blah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " y'know what, 100 million people went to see a movie about what i do, i wonder how many people would go see a movie called, jurassic parka.", "answer": " oh, that is so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " y'know if what i do is so lame, then why did you insist on coming with me this morning? huh? was it so i just wouldn\u0092t go with mark?", "answer": " no. i... i wanted to be with you. i don\u0092t know, i feel like lately, i feel like you\u0092re slipping away from me, y'know. with this new job, and all these new people, and you\u0092ve got this whole other life going on. i-i-i know it\u0092s dumb, but i hate that i\u0092m not a part of it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " it\u0092s not dumb. but, maybe it\u0092s okay that you\u0092re not a part of it. y'know what i mean?  i mean it\u0092s like, i-i-i like that you\u0092re not involved in that part of my life.", "answer": " that\u0092s a little clearer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " honey see, it doesn\u0092t mean that i don\u0092t love you. because i do. i love you, i love you so much. but my work it\u0092s-it\u0092s for me y'know, i\u0092m out there, on my own, and i\u0092m doing it and it\u0092s scary but i love it, because it\u0092s mine. i, but, i mean is that okay?", "answer": " sure, i-i-i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " your thinking about my leg aren\u0092t you?", "answer": " no. no. actually i forgot, what is the deal with that again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " it\u0092s okay if it bothers you. really. i mean the only thing i need to know is: \u0091how much it bothers you?\u0092 because i don\u0092t like wasting my time. am i wasting my time?", "answer": " no. no. i don\u0092t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " what\u0092s that?", "answer": " that\u0092s-that\u0092s my nubbin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " what\u0092s a nubbin?", "answer": " it\u0092s kinda a ah, a third nipple kinda thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " you have three nipples?", "answer": " well, y'know two regulars. and ah one that barely qualifies as...  ahh, what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " nothing. i, i just remembered i have to leave.", "answer": " you ah, you have, you have to leave, now? how come?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  oh, i thought you weren\u0092t coming. what? where were you?", "answer": " come here, come here.  okay, don\u0092t get mad, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " okay, don\u0092t give me a reason to get mad, okay", "answer": " i played smelly cat for the people at my old ad agency, they went nuts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " no, look, i told you that i didn\u0092t want you to try and sell it, and you just, you big fat did it anyway. god, y'know what, i think five years ago i probably would\u0092ve done anything to play with you but, i can do it by myself. and if i can\u0092t trust you then just forget it.", "answer": " no, no, i don\u0092t want to forget it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " sorry, pheebs.", "answer": " yeah. you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " yeah. i actually am, yeah. y'know life-life\u0092s gonna had you all kinds of stuff, y'know you learn your little lessons and hopefully you grow. wanna hear a new song?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " we\u0092d love too.", "answer": " okay.  \u0091jingle bitch screwed me over! go to hell jingle whore! go to hell go to hell. go to hell-hell-hell.\u0092 that\u0092s all i have so far. closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  well hello!", "answer": " where have you been?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " the doctor.", "answer": " is everything okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh yes! just had me a little nubbin-ectomy. yep! two nipples, no waiting.", "answer": " wow! it\u0092s like rachel in high school.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " what?!!", "answer": " come on! come on, i was kidding! it was such an obvious joke!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}]